Open Up.
Swallow is a drama, thriller, horror film directed by Carlo Mirabella-Davis.
Hunter, a newly pregnant housewife, finds herself
increasingly compelled to consume dangerous objects.
As her husband and his family tighten their control over her life, she
must confront the dark secret behind her new obsession.
Hunter Conrad, played by Haley Bennett.
Richie Conrad, played by Austin Stowell.
Katherine Conrad, played by Elizabeth Marvel.
Michael Conrad, played by David Rasche.
Erwin William, played by Denis O'Hare.
Lucy, played by Luna Lauren Vélez.
Swallow is a 2019 psychological thriller film written and directed by Carlo Mirabella-Davis and
starring Haley Bennett, Austin Stowell, Elizabeth Marvel, David Rasche, and Denis O'Hare.
Its plot follows a young woman who, emotionally stifled in her marriage and
domestic life, develops an impulse to consume inedible objects.
The film had its world premiere at the Tribeca Film Festival on April 28, 2019.
It was released in France on January 15, 2020, by UFO Distribution, and
in the United States on March 6, 2020, by IFC Films.
The film explores themes of sexual abuse, housewife,
loneliness, psychological thriller, psychiatrist.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.